My Lord.
Oh no,
I entered the wrong place.
What should I do?
I'm actually not here for the girls.
That explanation sounds even worse.
So he has a new target.
Wait,
why does he look familiar?
Mister!
My Lord,
we have all kinds of girls here.
Look.
No need.
Move.
Uh, okay.
Um, Mister,
listen to my explanation.
Hey, Mister,
let me go!
So what are those two
making a scene here for?
That little lord just said
he wasn't interested in girls.
I know I was wrong, Mister.
I shouldn't have sneaked out of Yanmen.
It seems you yearn for the outside world.
I happen to be going out,
so you can come along as my attendant.
Attendant?
Why do I have a bad feeling about this?
Looks like Madam is
going to suffer on this trip.
Mister,
thank you for bringing me to the market.
I told you I'm out on business.
Hmph,
you don't mean what you say.
I
want this.
Good eye, Miss.
Our sugar figures are crisp, sweet,
and don't stick to your teeth.
One coin each.
Mister,
one rabbit,
one black fox.
Two in total.
Mister, do you want to eat too?
A long time ago,
someone told me
that sugar figures only taste good
when two people eat them together.
Mmm, so sweet.
Mister, try it quickly.
Still too sweet,
just like back then.
Mister, look,
a puppet show!
Let's go watch it.
Slow down, the show won't run away.
Okay.
Master,
how can there be an inn
in the middle of nowhere?
Who cares?
I'm starving to death.
As long as there's food inside.
Let's go in and see.
Oh,
three guests.
Are you eating or staying?
Braised pork, steamed fish,
braised pork joint, osmanthus cake.
Anything is fine,
just make it quick.
Master,
there's something wrong with this place.
I smell it.
The lingering scent of demons.